called the Order of the Regards.
It's going to be the Minor City Council for Monday, October 17th, 2022.
Two proclamation to the Clingott-Tobber, as I know me, but it's in the awareness month.
I was practicing in the back, and I'm not sure do we have someone here for that.
You want to speak?
You say a little?
I'm Reverend Cassie Tritthart, and I operate a business here in town, but I also have.
Does that sound a little bit?
It's a disorder that affects the autonomic nervous system.
Anything your body does for you without you actually telling it to do it, it just doesn't.
That can be, like, how your eyes dilate, how your heart beats, how you breathe, how you digest.
So it's something that most doctors in our area have never heard of.
And it's why I traveled to Texas every couple of months to see doctors.
So to seven years, when I was living here, to get a diagnosis, had to go to Mayo Clinic.
And disorder, know me, and her national, was asking all the local governments.
And the state governments, to declare October, is disorder, know me, and awareness month.
So I would ask for your consideration with that.
We greatly appreciate it.
Thank you. Yes, you have a microphone.
If you hang around the end, we'll give to you and take a picture.
Number three, approximation to claim November has long cancer awareness month.
Are you here for this one, too?
No?
No.
Second.
Number five.
Parker.
Four public input or unscheduled personal appearances.
Number one.
Mr. Shandu Han.
Subject.
Be the great deer hunt.
Good evening.
I just want to quickly remind you all that next week is the great deer hunt.
That is the veterans hunt.
We do every year for our disabled and paralyzed veterans.
It's a labor of love.
It's something we look forward to every year.
And that's going to kick off Thursday, October 27th at 9 a.m. at Commerce High School.
This year, my am a public school.
This is already agreed to host the event next year.
So we're excited about that.
But one of the cool.
So things about this year, we've got a lot of great speakers and presentations at the opening
ceremony.
I believe my am a fire department and grow fire department or providing ladder trucks
to the voice of the flag to kick off the event.
We'll go inside the Commerce High School gym for the ceremony.
Lieutenant Governor Matt Penel will be here as well as representatives from Senator Langford's
office and Congressman Mark Wayne Mullins office.
So all, and of course, Steve Becher, Josh West, Michael Berksham, those guys will all
be there, including Bo Reese, he'll be there as well.
Hopefully all of you will get a chance to attend.
We'd love to have you.
On Friday we have our big.
All of our meals are open to the public Friday.
We have the catfish launch.
We'll cook up a lot of fish for you.
Come on out.
It's a great time.
Mark Wayne Mullins will be there serving fish to the veterans.
So if you have want to opportunity to spend some time.
Time with your Congress, Munchoos, we're also currently running for Senate.
That might be a good opportunity to catch his ear.
I also want to make sure to invite you to the Saturday evening meal, which all takes place
out a jacked out Ripple's house.
That meal is the final big event of the weekend.
It's also when we do our big auction.
But more importantly, if you come to the opening ceremony, you get to meet the hunters before
they start and experience what takes place over the weekend.
But on Saturday night, that's where the emotions kick in.
And it's a very powerful ceremony.
The hunters themselves will get up and talk about their experiences while they're here.
If you want to know what other people coming to my am are really thinking about my amma, there won't
be a dry eye in the house.
If any of you guys have been there, I don't know Chris that has.
It's an amazing experience that they hear in their words how much they appreciate what this
community, all of the area communities do for them is powerful.
Which is kind of ironic given that we do all of this to try to say thank you to them for all
they've done to serve our country.
And so to hear them thanking us for what we do, it's quite an emotional scene.
So please come out.
Meet with us, enjoy the fellowship, get to meet our hunters.
We have 600 this year, it's going to be a good time and there's an open invitation to every
event we have out there, just come on out, we'd love to see you, I'd be happy to answer any
other questions.
All right.
Thank you.
Five considered gender staff recommends we approve out of six and seven.
eight budget amendment number 23 dash 08 a capital improvement project purchase of Harvey's hair design property so the flip side this is actually part a that is the first part where the city the council is moving money from it's CIP improvement fund to MSU A to purchase that property
it's like nine word lease purchase agreement star was built for the payment of ex-water back home will loader to SUV for explorers and give related
signing and payment authority to city manager or his design.
It's like
MOU between city and the youth athletic development foundation for the use of the city civic center gymnasium for the youth basketball for the fiscal year 22 23 season
this mission of insurance and foot food halers permit.
This is the annual MOU with the YADF the youth basketball.
No languages changed the MOU for the past couple years the only difference in this MOU is we have defined dates for his season.
Normally his annual agreement would run 365 days with more and more activity coming into the civic center we ask him to give us an actual season so now he has dates for his MOU is active.
So you see it starts in November and ends in January and January but nothing in the language has changed and we have all of his insurance and everything has normal.
I like motion to approve.
11 MOU between the city and Allen science studio for the removal.
Refurbish and display of Thunderburg date or sign marky polls and all other support structures.
So this is the sign that has been at the Thunderbird since we were all young.
Colby has a sign garden that he has started at Allen sign the city is going to retain ownership of the sign but allow him to take the sign refurbish it at his expense and display it there in the sign garden.
So why are we retaining ownership of.
We have to according to the grant.
All right, thank you, Christy.
Twelve, mayor's nomination to read a point, 10-manigrum to the city,
zoning and planning commission.
13, mayor's nomination to read a point,
Brian Eastup to the city, zoning and planning commission.
14, mayor's nomination to read a point,
Lee Ann Walker to the board of adjustments.
15, other new business of any of which is the residence
of the posting of this agenda.
16, mayor and council community announcements.
I've got one, I want to talk about coach Lauren Stratk.
She's head softball coach at Montenegro School and her lady ward off softball team.
They qualify for the state tournament and went down to Oklahoma City
and played there at the Hall of Fame stadium complex.
They're both in the state semifinals before they got beat,
but they represent our community very well.
While they were there, I don't think a lot of people
expected them to be there other than themselves,
but they did a good job at played hard.
They lost in an extra inning game.
To get qualified for state, they went down to beat a really good
particular team and actually in the final game, they jumped on pretty good.
So I wanted to congratulate coach Stratk and her team,
and thank them for representing our community that they did.
17, city manager's communication.
I do not have anything at this time.